<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Scottie Spinazola&#39;s website</title>
    <link>http://scottiespinazola.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Scottie Spinazola&#39;s website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://scottiespinazola.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The one true perfect bracket, well at least that&#39;s what my mom told me</title>
      <link>http://scottiespinazola.github.io/2022/04/04/the-one-true-perfect-bracket-well-at-least-that-s-what-my-mom-told-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://scottiespinazola.github.io/2022/04/04/the-one-true-perfect-bracket-well-at-least-that-s-what-my-mom-told-me/</guid>
      <description>So the time has finally come. I am excited and nervous.
I feel like I am playing in the tournament but that is far from the truth. I played organized basketball for about three years, I think I scored a handful of baskets. I played before my growth spurt so I think that has a lot to do why I am not playing in college right now and preparing for a long NBA career.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Chris Paul Effect </title>
      <link>http://scottiespinazola.github.io/2021/04/20/chris-paul-effect/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://scottiespinazola.github.io/2021/04/20/chris-paul-effect/</guid>
      <description>There is no I in the word team but once or twice or honestly however many you want to say in every generation a player makes you think that maybe it does just come down to one person.
Who comes to mind for me is Michael Jordan, Lebron James, Tom Brady, and you can even put Mike Trout in there for making the angels a pretty solid team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Deserves the Spot in the HOF of the Top Three QBs in the 2004 Draft</title>
      <link>http://scottiespinazola.github.io/2021/03/16/who-deserves-the-spot-in-the-hof-of-the-top-three-qbs-in-the-2004-draft/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://scottiespinazola.github.io/2021/03/16/who-deserves-the-spot-in-the-hof-of-the-top-three-qbs-in-the-2004-draft/</guid>
      <description>As a Sports fan I do not intend on making this into something that will make people mad or to bring down a players career by nit picking through there career.
This is just intended to see that with three careers in my generation that are close and honestly to me seem pretty interesting to see who stat wise would be inducted in canton at the Pro Football Hall of fame.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
